vibes2lyrics.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy - VIBES2LYRICS.COM NIGERIA

**AD:-** **Promote Your Music On This Website For A Token[Click Here](http://goo.gl/hPZBao) For More Info. Tell/WhatsApp:- 08021253418; BBM PIN:D8BC5131**  
**Join Our BBM Channel For Hot Updates, PIN:**[ **C004AD282**](http://pin.bbm.com/C004AD282)

## Personal Information

  * **Browsing VIBES2LYRICS** You can watch videos on VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS without having a VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account or using a Social Network Accounts (Facebook, Twitter, e.t.c). You also can contact us through the VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Help Center or by emailing us directly without having to register for an account.
  * **Usually, The Lyrics / Musical Section doesn’t require a signup as its rather necessary to implement but could happen in future**
  * **Your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account.** For some activities on VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, like uploading videos, posting comments, flagging videos, or watching restricted videos, you need a VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. 
  * **Usage Information.** When you use VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the channels, groups and favorites you subscribe to, which other users you communicate with, the videos you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers, and information you display about yourself as well as information you click on in VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS (including UI elements, settings). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account. In order to ensure the quality of our service to you, we may place a tag (also called a “web beacon”) in HTML-based customer support emails or other communications with you in order to confirm delivery.
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others. If you download the VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Uploader, your copy includes a unique application number. This number, and information about your installation of the Uploader (version number, language) will be sent to VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS when the Uploader automatically checks for updates and will be used to update your version of the Uploader.

## Uses

  * If you submit personal information to VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, and to process any flagging activity or other communication you send to us.
  * We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS changes or for customer service purposes). You also can choose how often VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS sends you email updates in your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account settings page.
  * We use cookies, web beacons, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

## Information That is Publicly Available

  * When you create a VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account, some information about your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS. This may include the date you opened your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account, the date you last logged into your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of videos you have watched.
  * Your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, such as when you upload videos or send messages through VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.
  * Any videos that you submit to VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS users or the general public. 
  * You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account channel page. If you choose to add certain features to your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account channel page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other users and may be aggregated and shared with your friends or other users. Such shared activity may include your favorite videos, videos you rated and videos that you have uploaded.

## Your Choices

  * If you have a VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information, email preferences and privacy settings at any time by visiting your account profile page. 
  * You may control the information that is available to other users and your confirmed friends at any time by editing your VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS Account and the features that are included on your channel page. If you have enabled Active Sharing, other users may see that you, as identified by your account name, not your email address, are watching the same video.
  * You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, in which case you can still view videos and explore VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS, but VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS may not be able to provide certain services to you. Some advanced VIBES2LYRICS VIDEOS features may use other services like YOUTUBE VIDEOS, Checkout or AdSense. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

  * About
  * Latest Posts

### [krimdelakrym](http://vibes2lyrics.com/)

Tipped To Be The Next Bill-Gates!!!. WebSite Developer, Software Programmer and Blogger. Graduate Of Construction Technology and Brain Behind VIBES2LYRICS.COM + many other regular website you use everyday.

#### Latest posts by krimdelakrym ([see all](http://vibes2lyrics.com/author/krimdelakrym/))

### Comments

comments
